<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-10-09T22:02:40-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">Top 10 2023</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/top-10-2023.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Top 10 2023" /><published>2023-12-21T12:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2023-12-21T12:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/top-10-2023</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/top-10-2023.html"><![CDATA[<div class="container">
  <div class="flex-grid top10-container">
    <div>
      <span><a href="../top-10-2023">2023</a> | <a href="../top-10-2022">2022</a> | <a href="../top-10-2021">2021</a></span>
      <h1 class="top10-big-header">My Top 10 Albums of 2023</h1>
    </div>
  
    <p class="top10-intro-blurb">   
      This year felt like a really big year for me musically.</br></br>
      At the start of the year I set out to try and push myself a little and listen to more albums I'd normally not bother with, 
      which ended up being a pretty great call.</br></br>
      While there are definitely some of the big names you'd expect on my list this year, 
      there's also a couple artists I'd never heard of until this year, and some genres I might not have been into before, 
      which is kind of neat to me.</br></br>
  
      As always, I kept a playlist with my favourite track from each album I listened to <a class="top10-link" href="https://open.spotify.com/playlist/0zfTLj1IuQjbhTEzsQu9wM?si=a84470c5c888459a">here</a> if you're curious.
      </br></br>
  
      First, here are some songs from albums that didn't make the cut I loved...
  
      <ul class="top10-intro-blurb">
        <li><a class="song-link" href="https://youtu.be/UJXccBGs_IY?">That Life - Unknown Mortal Orchestra (Psychedelic Rock)</a></li>
        <li><a class="song-link" href="https://youtu.be/NxbEShI-tNY">Burfict! - Danny Brown & JPEGMAFIA (Rap)</a></li>
        <li><a class="song-link" href="https://youtu.be/OQs1Wf3nisg">Fall Back - James Blake (Electronic)</a></li>
        <li><a class="song-link" href="https://youtu.be/e48Zk_M-dKw">Soundcheck - Billy Woods and Kenny Segal (Hip Hop)</a></li>
      </ul>
      
      <h2 class="top10-subtitle">And now, my top 10 albums of 2023...</h2>
    
    </p>

    <div class="flex-grid album-container">
      <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2023/crj.png">

      <div class="album-header-container"> 
        <span class="album-number">10</span>

        <div class="album-title-container">
          <span class="album-title">Carly Rae Jepsen - The Loveliest Time</span>
  
          <span class="album-genre">Pop - <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/Y8qZ22IFK6I">Listen</a> </span>
        </div>       
      </div>
        
      <span class="album-blurb">Ya girl is back, and this one's a banger. Psychedlic Switch is easily my favourite pop song of the year and never gets old, but this album's got range as well. Kollage absolutely nails a much dreamier, slower vibe and I love the synth-y organs on After Last Night.</span>
    </div>

    <div class="flex-grid album-container">
      <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2023/grouptherapy.png">

      <div class="album-header-container"> 
        <span class="album-number">9</span>

        <div class="album-title-container">
          <span class="album-title">grouptherapy - i was mature for my age, but i was still a child</span>
  
          <span class="album-genre">Hip Hop - <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/s9AMFQbxj1Y">Lisnine</a> </span>
        </div>       
      </div>
        
      <span class="album-blurb">This album is everything I want in a Hip Hop album. All 3 artists have unique, but compliementary, styles that mesh together so well. Each artist is able to switch from leading a track to complimenting another person on a different track so well. Production on the album is spot-on and always interesting as beats range from grungey guitar driven, to piano and drums, to ballroom seamlessly from track to track. This album is a little long at 16 songs, but the consistent switch-ups make sure it never feels dull or repetitive.</span>
    </div>


    <div class="flex-grid album-container">
      <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2023/underscores.png">

      <div class="album-header-container"> 
        <span class="album-number">8</span>

        <div class="album-title-container">
          <span class="album-title">underscores - Wallsocket</span>
  
          <span class="album-genre">Hyper Pop - <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/G9zDeHOAP_g">Li.eight</a> </span>
        </div>       
      </div>
        
      <span class="album-blurb">I don't really know how to describe this album other than fun. Wallsocket is super high-energy and at times feels like what I imagine sticking a fork into a wallsocket feels like when the energy gets amped up to 11 and there's just a wall of noise on tracks like Locals and Geez louise. Slower tracks like You don't even know who I am still manage to keep things interesting, and provide a nice contrast to the faster tracks, while keeping things interesting.</span>
    </div>

    <div class="flex-grid album-container">
      <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2023/geese.png">

      <div class="album-header-container"> 
        <span class="album-number">7</span>

        <div class="album-title-container">
          <span class="album-title">Geese - 3D Country</span>
  
          <span class="album-genre">Rock - <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/0GJx5NWF414">Li.seven</a> </span>
        </div>       
      </div>
        
      <span class="album-blurb">I looooooove the vocals on this album, there's something about the energy, delivery, and little bit of tongue in cheek that just perfectly fits. 2122 is such a fun first track, there's no lead up it's just full tilt pedal to the metal from the start. 3D Country feels to me like something that's simulatenously very old-school rock, but also something that wouldn't exist without having decades of rock to learn from and tinker with.</span>
    </div>

    <div class="flex-grid album-container">
      <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2023/green-lung.png">

      <div class="album-header-container"> 
        <span class="album-number">6</span>

        <div class="album-title-container">
          <span class="album-title">Green Lung - This Heathen Land</span>
  
          <span class="album-genre">Heavy Metal - <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/EfNv6YI-6Jg">Li.six</a> </span>
        </div>       
      </div>
        
      <span class="album-blurb">I think my elevator pitch for Green Lung would be like Ghost but 30% less cringe. I came into the album late in the year (I actually found it on someone else's top 10) but haven't been able to put it down since. There's no frills or big risks here, but this is just really, <i>really</i>, solid metal to me from start to finish. Usually I find albums like this have 1-2 tracks I'm really into and the latter half is just kind of phoned in, but I think this album is kind of the total opposite. The falsetto-y vocals in Hunters in the Sky are just the right amount of cheesey and fit so well in the whole vibe, this album's just a lot of fun.</span>
    </div>

    <div class="flex-grid album-container">
      <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2023/zach-bryan.png">

      <div class="album-header-container"> 
        <span class="album-number">5</span>

        <div class="album-title-container">
          <span class="album-title">Zach Bryan - Boys of Faith</span>
  
          <span class="album-genre">Country - <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/amXQjWWAGeU">Li.five</a> </span>
        </div>       
      </div>
        
      <span class="album-blurb">'But Brendan, this is just an EP!'' I know, I know, imaginary person, but is also <i>very</i> good and felt like exactly the kind of album I would have ignored in previous years knowing it was country. It turns out if you love sad girls and guitars, there are some sad boys and guitars albums that are just as good. Zach Bryan also released an album this year that I discovered from this and is solid, but for me the stripped down, honest sound of this EP is just a big step closer to what I love. Really solid features from absolute giants Bon Iver and Noah Kahan fit perfectly into their respective songs, but to me the real stars of this album is the instrumentation. Sure there's some piano, electric and slide guitar, but for my money the clean, acoustic guitars and all the character they bring are the highlights.</span>
    </div>

    <div class="flex-grid album-container">
      <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2023/tomb-mold.png">

      <div class="album-header-container"> 
        <span class="album-number">4</span>

        <div class="album-title-container">
          <span class="album-title">Tomb Mold - The Enduring Spirit of Calamity</span>
  
          <span class="album-genre">Death Metal - <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/">Li.four</a> </span>
        </div>       
      </div>
        
      <span class="album-blurb">You know it's going to be a banger death metal band when you can't even tell where the letters are in the band's logo. This album is everything I've rediscovered in my love of death metal, from the deep growling vocals, screechy fast guitars, and someone just beating the absolute shit out of the drums. Tomb Mold manage to incorporate influences from all sorts of other genres but come through with an album that feels to me like death metal through and through without being unoriginal.</span>
    </div>

    <div class="flex-grid album-container">
      <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2023/paramore.png">

      <div class="album-header-container"> 
        <span class="album-number">3</span>

        <div class="album-title-container">
          <span class="album-title">Paramore - This is Why</span>
  
          <span class="album-genre">Pop Punk - <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/toKJP3luQbI">Li.three</a> </span>
        </div>       
      </div>
        
      <span class="album-blurb">Way back in 2017, I loved Paramore's last album After Laughter for its much more disco-y, funky approach to pop punk and I think there are parts of that that persisted through to this album that I still love. However, this album feels more post-punk-y to me, with a more straightforward rock sound and some very outwardly critical themes on tracks like The News and Big Man, Little Dignity. It's really impressive to hear a band who's been together for like 20 years still putting out culturally and emotionally relevant albums, and it's of course a given that the impossibly talented Hayley William's vocals are flawless.</span>
    </div>

    <div class="flex-grid album-container">
      <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2023/king-gizzard.png">

      <div class="album-header-container"> 
        <span class="album-number">2</span>

        <div class="album-title-container">
          <span class="album-title">King Gizzard and the Lizard Wizard - PetroDraconic Apocalypse; or, Dawn of Eternal Night: An Annihilation of Planet Earth and the Beginning of Merciless Damnation</span>
  
          <span class="album-genre">Hard Rock - <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/U0AcBryPUxY">Li.two</a> </span>
        </div>       
      </div>
        
      <span class="album-blurb">Plain and simple, this album fucking rocks. This was by far the album I had the hardest time picking a favourite track from. Partially because they all rule, and partially because they all feel like such a cohesive whole. How great this album comes together is even more impressive when you realize just how much music King Gizzard release, they released 5 albums last year and two this year. This album is fast, loud and an absolute wild ride start to finish. It's very hard to not want to crank up the volume and get caught up in the energy.</span>
    </div>

    <div class="flex-grid album-container">
      <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2023/boygenius.png">

      <div class="album-header-container"> 
        <span class="album-number">1</span>

        <div class="album-title-container">
          <span class="album-title">boygenius - the record</span>
  
          <span class="album-genre">Indie - <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/bIX_ouNJsTs">Li.one</a> </span>
        </div>       
      </div>
        
      <span class="album-blurb">If you like sad girls, you'll probably like sad girls<sup>3</sup>. <br>All 3 of the boys are incredibly gifted songwriters, singers, and musicians and gel together like they've been playing together since day 1. Not Strong enough is easily my favourite song of the entire year, the 'always and angel/never a god' crescendo always gets me right in the feels, and I am truly happy I got the chance to see it live this year. I often think about what bands from today might stand the test of time and be the ones people still listen to 20 or 30 years later, and boygenius consistently comes to mind for me as a top choice.</span>
    </div>

  </div>
</div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023 | 2022 | 2021 My Top 10 Albums of 2023 This year felt like a really big year for me musically. At the start of the year I set out to try and push myself a little and listen to more albums I'd normally not bother with, which ended up being a pretty great call. While there are definitely some of the big names you'd expect on my list this year, there's also a couple artists I'd never heard of until this year, and some genres I might not have been into before, which is kind of neat to me. As always, I kept a playlist with my favourite track from each album I listened to here if you're curious. First, here are some songs from albums that didn't make the cut I loved... That Life - Unknown Mortal Orchestra (Psychedelic Rock) Burfict! - Danny Brown & JPEGMAFIA (Rap) Fall Back - James Blake (Electronic) Soundcheck - Billy Woods and Kenny Segal (Hip Hop) And now, my top 10 albums of 2023...]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Top 10 2022</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/top-10-2022.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Top 10 2022" /><published>2022-12-27T12:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2022-12-27T12:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/top-10-2022</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/top-10-2022.html"><![CDATA[<div class="header-title-container">
  <h1 class="header-title">My Top 10 Albums of 2022</h1>
</div>

<div class="container">
  <div class="row header-container">
    <p class="header-body">   
      
      This year was a little strange for me, music-wise...</br></br>
      I don't exactly remember what prompted it,
      but I ended up spending a bunch of time early in the year digging through my listening history. 12 years ago I started tracking all the songs I'd listen to, and it's been fun to occasionally look back and find things I'd forgotten about. </br></br>
      This time, I ended up discovering a bunch of old metal albums that I thought I'd grown out of, but decided to give them a go and found myself coming back to them again and again.</br></br>
      I still listened to a ton of albums that were released this year (62 to be exact), but I think this experience made me a little more willing to give albums I might have just dismissed in past years some more time to grow on me, and this list is at least a little bit a reflection of that. A little more diverse, a little louder.
      
      </br></br>
    </br></br>

      But first, some songs that stuck out to me this year, in no particular order:

      <ul class="song-list">
        <li><a class="song-link" href="https://youtu.be/P3QS83ubhHE">Stromae - Santé (Pop)</a></li>
        <li><a class="song-link" href="https://youtu.be/lsbJvA_ag3c">Kehlani - altar (R&B)</a></li>
        <li><a class="song-link" href="https://youtu.be/jJVe_6N8cLY">TAKE A CHANCE (feat. Anderson .Paak) - DOMi & JD BECK (Jazz, Neo Soul)</a></li>
        <li><a class="song-link" href="https://youtu.be/hrkuo0y8gMU">6L GTR - The Chats (Punk)</a></li>
      </ul>
      
      <p class="header-body">   
      And now, my top 10 albums of 2022...
    
    </p>
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container">          
    <h2 class="album-number">10</h2>
    <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2022/fka.jpeg">
    <h3 class="album-title">FKA Twigs - CAPRISONGS</h3>
    <p class="album-genre">experimental pop</p>
    <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/cZTKjzAJLCk">Listen</a>
    <p class="album-blurb">FKAs one of those artists I really need to be in the right mood for, but this album is really great. FKA jumps all over the place with different genres and this album is captivating from start to finish.</p>
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container">          
    <h2 class="album-number">9</h2>
    <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2022/purity-ring.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">Purity Ring - graves</h3>
    <p class="album-genre">synth pop, dream pop</p>
    <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/2J85bFXgzJw">Listen</a>
    <p class="album-blurb">They just don't miss. After having to reschedule multiple times we finally got to see Purity Ring this year and man was it good to be back. Their signature style of pop just never gets old for me, and this is no exception.</p>
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container">          
    <h2 class="album-number">8</h2>
    <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2022/kendrick.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">Kendrick Lamar - Mr Morale and the Big Steppers</h3>
    <p class="album-genre">rap, hip hop</p>
    <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/toEW7_-pvOY">Listen</a>
    <p class="album-blurb">For my money, Kendrick's the best rapper alive right now. Everything about this album is fantastic, a couple skippable songs are the only thing really keeping this from climbing higher to me. A suprise feature from Sampha is a personal highlight, it's cool to see him getting more attention.</p>
  </div>


  <div class="row album-container">          
    <h2 class="album-number">7</h2>
    <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2022/mom-jeans.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">Mom Jeans. - Sweet Tooth</h3>
    <p class="album-genre">pop punk</p>
    <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/kyqMKNCJAaA">Listen</a>
    <p class="album-blurb">Sweet Tooth is an appropriate name, because this album is pure fluff. No life changing catharses here, but it's catchy, goes down easy, and is a lot of fun.</p>
  </div>


  <div class="row album-container">          
    <h2 class="album-number">6</h2>
    <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2022/leikeli.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">Leikeli47 - Shape Up</h3>
    <p class="album-genre">rap, hip hop</p>
    <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/JAM_ONZgPnE">Listen</a>
    <p class="album-blurb">The beats and production on this album are just untouchable. The beats are catchy, unique and perfectly match Leikeli's bars. This album goes hard and is such an easy listen from start to finish.</p>
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container">          
    <h2 class="album-number">5</h2>
    <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2022/danger-mouse.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">Danger Mouse & Black Thought - Cheat Codes</h3>
    <p class="album-genre">hip hop</p>
    <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/qZFZh62tw3o">Listen</a>
    <p class="album-blurb">You had me at MF DOOM feature. For me, Belize is clearly the highlight of the album, though there's a plethora of other banger features on this album including RTJ, Raekwon and Joey Bada$$. This album is, to me, just Hip Hop in it's best form. The beats are simple, but in the way like a really, really good sushi course is. Everything is thought through and exactly where it needs to be, and compliments the absolute deluge of talented rappers perfectly.</p>
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container">          
    <h2 class="album-number">4</h2>
    <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2022/dream-widow.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">Dream Widow - Dream Widow</h3>
    <p class="album-genre">thrash metal</p>
    <a class="album-link" href="">Listen</a>
    <p class="album-blurb">I definitely didn't have "Dave Grohl releases an honest to goodness thrash metal album" on my 2022 bingo card, but here we are. Dave Grohl can do it all and this just reinforces that, though he's really not treading any new ground here, it's fast, loud, and scratches an itch. The production on the album is absolutely spot on as well, balancing clarity and raw energy. 
    </p>
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container">          
    <h2 class="album-number">3</h2>
    <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2022/rosalia.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">ROSALÍA - MOTOMAMI</h3>
    <p class="album-genre">pop</p>
    <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/e-CEd6xrRQc">Listen</a>
    <p class="album-blurb">With song sung in Spanish with titles like HENTAI and CHICKEN TERIYAKI, what isn't to love? Calling this album just a pop album is a little bit of a disservice, since my favourite part of this album is how seamlessly she's able to blend different genres into a bunch of super-catchy and compelling songs.</p>
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container">          
    <h2 class="album-number">2</h2>
    <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2022/bcnr.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">Black Country, New Road - Ants from Up There</h3>
    <p class="album-genre">post-rock, alt rock, experimental</p>
    <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/yjC4qXiBRu4">Listen</a>
    <p class="album-blurb">The theatre kids are back at it again. A fantastic follow up to my album of the year last year, BCNR returns with more of the same, but not in a bad way. The lead vocals talk-singing, combined with his unnatturally deep voice is just so gripping.</p>
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container">          
    <h2 class="album-number">1</h2>
    <img class="album-img" src="./img/top10/2022/soul-glo.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">Soul Glo - Diaspora Problems</h3>
    <p class="album-genre">hardcore, punk</p>
    <a class="album-link" href="https://youtu.be/xK6X-zACMRQ">Listen</a>
    <p class="album-blurb">This album, as the kids say, rips. It's loud, fast and relentless. There are some great features mixed in, which is kind of a different thing for the genre, and some less-than-surface level themes going on with the lyrics. This one took a little while to grow on me, but has been on repeat since.      </p>
  </div>

  <div class="album-bottom"></div>
</div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[My Top 10 Albums of 2022]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Top 10 2021</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/top-10-2021.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Top 10 2021" /><published>2021-12-30T12:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2021-12-30T12:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/top-10-2021</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/top-10-2021.html"><![CDATA[<div class="header-title-container">
  <h1 class="header-title">My Top 10 Albums of 2021</h1>
</div>

<div class="container">
  <div class="row header-container">
    <p class="header-body">    Another year, another half-baked place to host this, another top 10 list.
      </br></br>
      This year felt like a little bit of a return to normal for music. Last year's releases definitely carried a heavy influence from COVID-19, and despite things that I'm sure will look weird in 5-10 years like everyone being masked in Silk Sonic music videos, I didn't feel that as much this year.
    </br></br>
      Every year, I think the hardest part of doing this list is writing the little blurbs for each of the albums. I'm not the greatest writer, and find it even harder to write about things I'm really excited about for whatever reason. My girlfriend suggested that I try just describing them like I do to her, since according to her I'm pretty good at that. I'm not sure if she's just being nice to me or not, but I'm going to go with that.
    </br></br>
      Anyways, I thought I'd start this list with some tracks that really stuck out to me this year, presented in no particular order:
      <ul class="song-list">
        <li><a class="song-link" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zqBGLAG8OmY">Soshy - Purity Ring</a></li>
        <li><a class="song-link" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fhyk9rchC2c">Silk Chiffon - MUNA ft. Phoebe Bridgers</a></li>
        <li><a class="song-link" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jv1isVWZKjI">Charger - Elio ft. Charli XCX</a></li>
        <li><a class="song-link" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K6BRna4_bmg">Edamame - bbno$ ft. Rich Brian</a></li>
        <li><a class="song-link" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gNi_6U5Pm_o">good 4 u - Olivia Rodrigo</a></li>
      </ul>
      
      And now, my top 10 albums of 2021...
    
    </p>
  </div>
  
  <div class="row album-container">          
      <h2 class="album-number">10</h2>
      <img class="top-10-img" src="./img/top10/2021/tyler.jpg">
      <h3 class="album-title">Tyler, the Creator - CALL ME IF YOU GET LOST</h3>
      <a class="track-link" href="https://youtu.be/icoOOiSlKK0">Listen</a>
      <p>I'm not sure Tyler really needs an introduction, but the man just doesn't miss. Tyler's stellar production, unique style and smooth flows are back, and this time with a few more of what I believe the kids call 'bangers' than 2019's IGOR.</p>
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container">
    <h2 class="album-number">9</h2>
    <img class="top-10-img" src="./img/top10/2021/slowthai.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">Slowthai - TYRON</h3>
    <a class="track-link" href="https://youtu.be/oXx2TczveMI">Listen</a>
    <p>I can't say I listen to a lot of Grime, but Slowthai is the exception. His aggressive rap style goes great with an album that is slit right down the middle between ego and boast on one side, and introspection and reflection on the other.</p>
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container">
    <h2 class="album-number">8</h2>
    <img class="top-10-img" src="./img/top10/2021/parquet_courts.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">Parquet Courts - Sympathy for Life</h3>
    <a class="track-link" href="https://youtu.be/0R7wpcw1Z4A">Listen</a>
    <p>I guess I'd call this album dad rock, but made by New York hipsters. This album has some weird acid rock-y fills and transitions that I'm not the biggest fan of, but the meat of the album is fantastic.</p>
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container">
    <h2 class="album-number">7</h2>
    <img class="top-10-img" src="./img/top10/2021/illuminati_hotties.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">Illuminati hotties - Let Me Do One More</h3>
    <a class="track-link" href="https://youtu.be/RTTTEfurozI">Listen</a>
    <p>This album is a blast. It's definitely not the most approachable at times, but the highs are very high and the lead single, Pool Hopping, has been on repeat since it was released. Punk is a pretty strange genre to define, since the definition has changed so much, but this album sure feels like punk. There's definitely some indie rock-y vibes sprinkled in, but the eccentricity and pure energy involved sure feels like punk to me.</p>
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container">
    <h2 class="album-number">6</h2>
    <img class="top-10-img" src="./img/top10/2021/ariel_view.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">Ariel View - Bury My Head</h3>
    <a class="track-link" href="https://youtu.be/SL8IOuVbn8I">Listen</a>
    <p>I really slept on their previous album, Until My Lungs Are Clear. It showed up on my top 10 list, but since then it's been on heavy rotation and probably should have been higher on my original list. This album is no different, I love their combination of pop punk, indie rock and everything in between. </p>
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container">
    <h2 class="album-number">5</h2>
    <img class="top-10-img" src="./img/top10/2021/men_i_trust.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">Men I Trust - Untourable Album</h3>
    <a class="track-link" href="https://youtu.be/0LMwgWFzDjU">Listen</a>
    <p>Men I Trust have quickly become one of my all-time favourite bands. Their recent Tiny Desk Concert, and this fantastic album, has helped me cope with having not one but two shows cancelled on us due to COVID.  Their blend of smooth, jazzy intrumentals with dreamy sad girl vocals is amazing.</p>
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container">
    <h2 class="album-number">4</h2>
    <img class="top-10-img" src="./img/top10/2021/idles.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">ILDES - CRAWLER</h3>
    <a class="track-link" href="https://youtu.be/cLT6P0Q7Mt0">Listen</a>
    <p>Another Tiny Desk alumnus, I can't resist the pure energy and passion IDLES put into their music. I listened to a lot more guitar-y, punk-y, rock-ish stuff in 2021 than before and IDLES has definitely contributed to that. Just pure energy, with growling witty vocals.</p>
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container">
    <h2 class="album-number">3</h2>
    <img class="top-10-img" src="./img/top10/2021/doja_cat.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">Doja Cat - Planet Her</h3>
    <a class="track-link" href="https://youtu.be/0EVVKs6DQLo">Listen</a>

    <p>I'm not ashamed to admit that sometimes, when I really need to get work done, I would just turn on Juicy and listen to it back, to back, to back, to back, to back, to back.... ad infinitum.</br> This was my introduction to Doja Cat and I haven't really cooled on her since. Some very solid features from Young Thug, Ariana Grande and best of all, SZA, make for a fantastic pop album.</p>
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container">
    <h2 class="album-number">2</h2>
    <img class="top-10-img" src="./img/top10/2021/silk_sonic.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">Silk Sonic - An Evening with Silk Sonic</h3>
    <a class="track-link" href="https://youtu.be/IQQ-87RSCRM">Listen</a>

    <p>I'd expect that a lot of people's introduction to Anderson .Paak was his absolutely incredible Tiny Desk Concert, as was mine. Since then I've been a big fan, and hearing about his collaboration with Bruno Mars had me all sorts of interested. I'm not as much of a fan of Bruno Mars, but there's no denying the man can sing.</br>   The two of them together is everything I had hoped for and more, blending funk with Anderson's exceptional drumming and Bruno's vocal talent for an album I'm sure I'll have on repeat for a long, long time.</p>                        
  </div>

  <div class="row album-container album-bottom">
    <h2 class="album-number">1</h2>
    <img class="top-10-img" src="./img/top10/2021/black_country_new_road.jpg">
    <h3 class="album-title">Black Country, New Road - For the first time</h3>
    <a class="track-link" href="https://youtu.be/xDcGl8tZhrs">Listen</a>

    <p>These English kids have big Drama Kid energy. Their music combines elements of math rock, post-punk, rock and jazz with lead vocals that are truely unique to me. I love the energy and range this album brings, it reminds me of great albums like Dark Side of the Moon where the songs flow together so well that once you start the album it's almost hard not to finish it.</p>
  </div>
</div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[My Top 10 Albums of 2021]]></summary></entry></feed>